一年后
哈基姆 我们明天把枪发下去
Hakim, we'll need to distribute the guns tomorrow,
你先看一下
and guard them for now.
马可 麦迪 你俩留下来
Marco, Medhi, you're staying.
巴瑟姆会第一时间打给你
Basem will call you first thing.
我也留下 没问题
I'll stay too. Not a problem.
离开这里
Get the fuck out of here.
学巴瑟姆叔叔那样 继续
Do it like Uncle Basem. Go on.
快点
Let's go.
干杯
Cheers.
你他妈干嘛呢
The fuck are you doing?
看这个
Check this.
能给放回去吗
You putting it back together?
才不要
No? Don't think so. ...
别动
Stay seated.
好了
Okay.
我知道你们阿尔及利亚人很忙 很快就好
I see you Algerians are busy so this will take only a few minutes.
只有一个可以活着出去 明白吗
One of you can walk away. Okay?
你可以走了
Off, you can go.
谁卖你的
Who sold you this?
不说 行
No? Okay.
麻烦吞了
Swallow, please.
吞 听懂了吗
Swallow. Yes?
再一个
Again, please.
再来一个
Just one more
是了
Yes...
没事的哈
It's okay. It's okay.
问他知不知道谁卖你们的枪
Ask him if he knows who sold you the guns.
问不出答案 就开枪 我就放了你 我保证
No answer, you shoot. You go free. I promise.
我们什么都不知道 我发誓
We don't know anything...I swear we don't!
那就开枪吧 三
So shoot. Three...
二
Two...
一
One...
听好 定规矩的是我 秘密不是个好东西
Look, I'm here to make the rules now and secrets are a bad thing.
特别 特别不好
A really very, very bad thing.
去跟你巴瑟姆叔叔说
Go tell Uncle Basem.
跟他说 这话是科巴说的 明白吗
Tell him Koba says so. Mm?
去吧
Go.
去
Go...
去啊
Go!
伊斯坦布尔
凯恩女士  阿卜杜拉·沙法克 已...
阿卜杜拉·沙法克 已死
亚历克斯·杜马尼
杜马尼金融 首席执行官
这是我的城市
This is my city.
这是我的城市 是生我养我的地方
This is my city. I was born on these streets. They're inside me.
我见证它随着时代变迁
I've seen them change from year to year
熟知城市的命脉 因为它就在这里
and I know this city's heartbeat because it's here.
与我是一体
I feel it.
你的创业公司需要融1亿美元 对吧
Your startup is looking for 100 million.
我的竞争对手也许可以出资
My competitors will offer you the moon.
有些人会扔个仨瓜俩枣
Some will throw in a few stars
但我是唯一一个会全心实意帮你的人
but I'm the only one that can join this...to this.
再加上 2亿入场费
Plus...a buy-in of 200 million.
感谢您的信任
Thank you for your trust.
谢谢
Thank you.
失陪一下 先随便喝点什么好吧
2 minutes. Help yourselves to drinks, yeah?
我到早了
I'm early.
阿卜杜拉·沙法克 我客户 昨晚在土耳其被杀
Abdullah Shafak, one of my clients, was killed in Turkey last night.
你知道吗
Were you aware?
你帮沙法克洗的2亿美元不是他的
The 200 million you laundered for Shafak wasn't his to give
在别处投资的钱也不是你的
nor was it yours to invest elsewhere.
我们投资人想收回来 有问题吗
Our investors would like it back. Does it give you any trouble?
没有什么我处理不了的
Nothing I can't handle.
你担心你新朋友会发现他们到底在跟谁做生意
You re worried your new friends will see who they're dealing with.
他们是跟杜马尼金融做生意 钱都是干干净净的
They're dealing with Dumani Finances. Clean funds all the way.
-无知是福  -我也不喜欢惊喜
- Ignorance is bliss. - And I don't like surprises,
所以下次要是出这种事 不妨先跟我打声招呼
so next time something like this needs to happen, how about you tell me?
合情合理
Reasonable.
记住了 所有人都以为
Remember though, everyone thought
华莱土会把你拖下水
that the Wallaces would take you down with them.
我从没怀疑过你
I never doubted you.
我记得清清楚楚
I remember everything.
转完账跟我说一声
Let me know when you've transferred the funds.
亚历克斯
Alex...
亚历克斯 救我
Alex...Help me.
不好意思
Oh, excuse me.
你能搞定吗 爱德
Can you fix this, Ed?
你不觉得现在才问有点晚了吗
It's a bit late for that, don't you think?
你能搞定吗
Can you fix it?
感谢各位出席
I appreciate your presence here
这样我们就能解决这个不必要的麻烦了
so that we can sort out this unnecessary mess.
这鬼地方谁选的
Who chose this shithole?
你们应该都知道他是谁了吧
I think you all know his name by now.
科巴
Koba.
别忘了他被邀请来伦敦的原因
Don't forget why he was invited to London.
如果不是尸横遍野
If the bodies were not piling up on the streets,
但凡你们听进去警告
if you would have listened to the warnings,
就没必要让科巴出马
there would be no need for Koba.
我已经跟他们保证过
I've given them my word.
投资者们需要秩序
The Investors asked for order
而我要给他们的就是秩序
and order is what I'm giving them.
我希望你们都能遵守规矩
I expect you all to fall in line.
麻烦站起来好吗
Would you mind standing, please?
有些人也许认识苏达尼先生
Some of you may know Mr Soudani.
之前这桌上没出现过这种东西
You haven't seen them round this table
但今天他会给你们解惑
but today he's here to help.
谁卖给你的
Who sold you this?
双方没见过面
It was a blind deal.
真刺激 说说看
Ooh! Exciting. Tell me about that
不知道姓名 没打过照面 国外付款
Er...No names, no faces. And er...payment was off-shore.
好 非常好
Good. Very good.
我要想糊弄阿菲迪先生 也会这么说
Exactly what I would do, if I wanted to insult Mr Afridi.
要我想糊弄自已
If I wanted to make a fool of me.
也会这么说
That's what I would do.
老板交待过
Boss here said this.
除了我 这个城市不许倒卖枪支
Nobody sells guns in this city except me.
是哪个字不清楚 是哪点不理解
Which bit of that was fuzzy? Which bit didn't add up?
你欠我 欠阿菲迪先生一条命 明白吗
You owe a debt to myself, to Mr Afridi. Yes?
但那是之后的事
But that's for later.
生意要讲规矩
Business has rules.
你们也遵守了
I see they are followed.
这位朋友犯了错 他自己也清楚
Our friend here made a mistake. He knows that.
不管谁卖的枪 都是不守规矩
But whoever sold these guns doesn't want rules.
他们觉得自己很特别
They think they are special.
要我跟你们讲讲还有谁觉得自己很特别吗
Shall I tell you who else thought they were special?
芬恩·华莱士
Finn Wallace.
他那个疯儿子
His lunatic son.
他们现在还坐在这里吗
Do they sit with us now?
爱德·杜马尼知道我在说什么
Ed Dumani knows what I'm talking about.
他那会儿犯过错吗 也许
Did he make mistakes back then? Maybe so.
但他清楚必须做出改变
But he understands things had to change.
你还有未来 对吧 爱德华
There's a future for you, right, Edward?
还有你儿子亚历克斯
And your son, Alex.
有人不安分想挑起战争
Somebody here wants to start a war.
注定要失败的一场仗
One they cannot win.
我向阿菲迪先生保证过
I gave Mr Afridi my word.
我会找出你
I will find you.
而你会付出代价
And you will make amends.
他完全不懂这座城市
He doesn't know the first thing about this city.
你觉得我为什么选他
Why do you think I chose him?
没有隶属关系
No affiliations.
-他就自己一人  -他是个疯子
- He's a clean skin. - He's a wind-up.
去找出谁卖的枪
Help me find out who's behind the guns.
这些人还是听爱德·杜马尼的话的 对不对
These people still listen to Ed Dumani...don't they?
太惨了 他家人在里面
Such a tragedy. His family is waiting.
真主保佑 马可是个好孩子
Blessings be upon you. Marco was a good boy.
法兹 帮我把这个拿下去 法兹
Faz, help me get this down...Faz?
他们说是车祸
They're saying it's a car accident?
其实不是 对吧
Wasn't that, was it?
法兹
Faz.
到底出什么事了
What's going on? Huh? What?
-你早就知道对不对  -你说什么呢
- You knew, innit? - What you talking about?
你早知道科巴要去 所以你才不想我待在那儿
You knew Koba was coming. That's why you didn't want me there.
行 那咱们去跟马可小女儿说到底怎么回事
All right. Let's go and tell Marco's little daughters what happened.
法兹为了保命把马可的脑袋打爆了
That big man Faz blew Marco's fucking brains out to save his own skin.
看我 巴瑟姆不知道那天会发生什么
Look at me. Basem doesn't know what day it is.
他他妈的给我们带沟里去了
He's got us in the wrong fucking sight.
现在我们得替那个阿尔巴尼亚混蛋圆谎
Now we got to cover for that Albanian prick.
我们刚到
We just arrived.
是 搬家公司的人也在
Yeah, the removal guys are here too.
好 今晚过来吧 我们挺想见你的
Okay, come tonight. We'd love to see you.
没问题 不会
No problem, no.
别只穿袜子就在楼梯上跑 会滑
No socks on the shiny stairs.
我们刚到
We just arrived.
萨兰达打来的 他们今天下午过来
From Saranda. They're coming over this afternoon.
之前不是说明天
But we said tomorrow, right?
那我也不能不让来啊 她还挺期待的
What, so I say don't come? She's too excited.
扎米尔会带吉他过来
Zamir's bringing his guitar.
亲爱的
My sweetheart.
我嫂子做的
My sister-in-law made that.
谢谢
Thank you.
房子不错
Nice place.
谢谢
Thank you.
巴瑟姆掩饰的挺好
Basem did a fantastic cover-up job.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
卢安 我知道枪是你卖给他的
Luan, I know you sold him those guns.
-那你是代表谁来的呢  -我是来帮你的
- And who am I talking to? - I'm here to help you.
帮我 还是帮你自己
Help me... or yourself?
你选边站的速度太快了
You choose sides so fast.
以前从没有用到过这种武器
That kind of weaponry is unprecedented.
我搭档需要自保
My partners need to defend themselves.
我要自保
I need to defend myself.
所以就要策划战争
So you're plotting a war?
我清楚现在局势有多不稳定 但这对大家生意都没好外
I know how volatile things are right now but that's not good for anyone's business.
我现在做的是海洛因生意
Heroin is my business now.
我一直只用自己的供应商
I've always used my own suppliers.
家乡那些值得信赖 效率高的人
Trusted, productive people from back home.
现在科巴要我从阿西夫那里进货
Now Koba wants me to buy from Asif.
只能从他那儿进
Only him.
你知道为什么吗
Do you know why?
因为这样他就能控制我
So he can control me.
我不会听他的
I won't do it.
因为下次他再来
Because next time he's gonna come around,
要的就不是我的货了 而是分我的钱
it's not my supply he'll want. It's my profit.
他的鞋已经踩我脖子上了
And he already got his boot on my neck.
这个城市里 生意不是
This is not how we do business
这么做的
in this city.
要我给你打保票呢
What if I offer you reassurances?
帮科巴打保票
From Koba?
-扯淡  -帮投资者
- Bullshit. - From the Investors.
我才不会像其他人一样摇尾乞怜
I'm not gonna lay down and beg like the others.
那你就得有所回报 卢安
Then you're going to have to give something in return, Luan.
枪是谁的
Who supplied those guns?
先说重要的事
First things first.
你去跟投资者谈 我要得到他们的保证
Talk to the Investors. I need guarantees.
很高兴你肯妥协
I'm glad you're listening.
想想这一切
Thinking about all this.
这一切就是我战斗的原因
All this is why I fight.
怎么回事 艾略特
What's going on Elliot?
你应该在沙法克先生到的时候干掉他
You were told to hit Mr Shafak on arrival in his car.
你迟到了 还喝醉了 还给我们带来了不必要的关注
You were late. You were drunk. You drew undue attention to us.
我们负责筹划 你负责按计划行事
We plan these things. You follow the plan.
要不然后果自负
Or there are consequences.
你跟你父亲都属于我们 艾略特
We own you and your father, Elliot.
有什么问题吗
Do you have a problem with that?
没
No.
那就行
Good.
钱已经转去以前的那个账号了
The fee has been released to the usual accounts.
稍等
Wait one second...
你收到行程单了吗
Did you receive the itinerary?
点击打开
伦敦 希思罗机场 头等舱
很久了 不是吗
Been a while, hasn't it?
我会告知我的人你的到达信息
I've let our contacts know you'll be arriving.
自打你上次离开后 事情的顺序已经发生了变化
The order of things has shifted since you were last there.
艾略特
Elliot...
我知道你离开的时候 一切都很难
I know when you left it was difficult
但不要被过去困住自己
but don't get distracted by the past.
请在这里签字
Signature there.
不要告诉我家里人 懂吗
Don't tell my family anything. Understood?
警察杀手
Cop killer!
意式浓缩 谢谢
Espresso, please.
所以是卢安在倒卖枪支 我一点都不意外
So Luan is distributing the guns. I wish I could say I was surprised.
只是一个交易 他需要保护自己的生意
It's a play for Ieverage. He needs peace to run his business.
他想留住自己的进货渠道 他不想从你这里进货
He wants to maintain his own supply. He doesn't want to buy from you.
-价格很好啊  -现在是
- It's a good price. - For now.
但卢安也不蠢
But Luan's not stupid.
他现在在这个镇上有很大的影响力
He has a major stake in this town now.
人手 盟友 他不容小觑
Manpower. Allies. He's not to be underestimated.
怎么能拿下他
What would he settle for?
投资人的保证
A guarantee from the Investors.
用他的忠诚来换取一定程度的独立
A degree of independence in return for his loyalty.
给了他这些 他就能停止枪支买卖了吗
And all this nonsense with guns...stops?
他还会告诉我们他的供货商
And he will tell us who supplied them.
他会的 相信我
He will Trust me.
我信你 我会告诉科巴先停止行动
Of course. I'll instruct Koba to hold off for now.
但在他交出供货商名字前 他是不安全的
But until he gives us his supplier, Luan is on thin ice.
爱德 谢谢你调查这件事
Thank you for looking into this, Ed.
你知道 芬恩·华莱士是个老傻子
You know, Finn Wallace was an old fool.
唯一做对的事情是他选了你
But he was smart...when he chose you.
没有欲望 没有恐惧
♪ ...no lust, no fear ♪
没有思想 没有贪婪 没有苦难
♪ No mind, no greed, no suffering ♪
妈的
Oh, fuck.
没有刀 没有词 没有谎言 没有治愈
♪ No knife, no words, no lie, no cure ♪
没有需求 没有憎恨 没有希望 没有话说
♪ No need, no hate, no will, no speech... ♪
-再见  -再见 丹妮
- Bye. - Bye, Danny.
我来拿吧 足球玩的怎么样
Here, I'll carry it. How was football?
-妈妈  -你好
- Mum? - Hey. Hi!
不好意思 等下 杜马尼女士
Sorry. Excuse me? Ms Dumani?
什么事
Yes?
杜马尼先生 你的女儿 带走了丹尼
Mr Dumani. Your daughter, she's taken Danny.
谢谢 加米亚
Thank you, Jamya
我怎么办 她就
What should I do? She just...
我来处理
I'll take it from here.
香农出来了
Shannon's out.
我和她律师聊了一下
I spoke to her lawyer.
警察在举证的时候程序出了问题
The police messed up evidence procedures.
她的案子根本立不住脚
Her case would have fallen apart at trial.
这是个好消息
That's the best news.
她告诉她的律师不要联系家人
She told her lawyer not to contact the family.
我告诉她等事情淡了一点之后我会救她出来的
I told her I would get her out once things had calmed down.
她杀了个警察 亚历克斯 我不会变魔术
She killed a cop, Alex. I don't have a magic wand.
她知道我无能为力
She knew my hands were tied.
她说她理解的 她跟我说她理解
She told you she understood. She told me she understood.
但那个不是她要听的
That's what we wanted to hear.
什么意思
What?
为了保护我们 她杀了那个警察
She killed that cop to protect us.
我们的生活没有受到影响
Our lives carried on as usual.
听着 她会回家的
Look...She'll come home.
我们应该庆祝一下
We should celebrate.
我做了我能力范围内能做的一切
I did everything in my power.
-是的  -今天真的够了
- You did. - What a day.
她回来了
She's back.
We got her back.
这意味着我们的又能是一家人了
This means we can be a family again.
-亚历克斯舅舅  -你怎么样啊 我的孩子
Uncle Alex How you doing, big man? Hey!
丹尼 我需要和阿里克斯舅舅聊聊 把这个拿走
Danny, um, I need to speak to Uncle Alex. Take this for me.
你的律师告诉我你在这里
Your lawyertold me you were here.
你买通了她 真能干
Oh, you paid her? That's nice.
我得见到你 对不起 要不你打我一顿
I had to see you. I'm sorry. You can beat me up if you like.
没必要 我不会再做那样的事了
No, don't. Don't. Im not doing it like that.
-只要你开心 我做什么都可以  -我只想和丹尼在一起
- I'll do it however you like. - I want to be with Danny.
这样你就能回到你的世界里 爱干啥干啥
So you can go back to your tower and do...whatever it is you do.
工作
Work
你和父亲觉得这个比我的命还重要
You and Dad decided it's a fuck sight more important than my life.
-听着  -这是你们的决定
- Look... - That was the deal you made.
是的 我们让步了
You're right. We gave in.
我为之工作的人 投资人
The people I work for, the Investors,
他们不想让杜马尼家族的人逍遥法外
they didn't want a Dumani walking free on a cop killing.
我让家族蒙羞了
I'm bad for the brand.
我会处理好的 所有的这一切
I'm getting us out. Out of all of this.
我已经很接近了 香农
And I'm so close, Shannon.
很快我们就能脱离这一切 我保证
Soon I'll have us out of this whole fucking world. I promise.
不再洗钱 不再有投资人
No more laundering. No more Investors.
我会照顾好我们大家
I'll take care of all of us.
我做的一切
Everything I'm doing...
我会纠正这一切
I can make this right.
所有的 我保证
Better than right, I swear.
现在都是我的事情了
It's on me now.
我自己能解决
I'll sort myself out.
如果你要帮我 离我远点
If you do want to help...leave us alone.
我听说你今晚要见投资人
I hear you're meeting with the Investors tonight
聊聊你的洗钱计划
about your start-up financing scheme.
你觉得这时候合适吗
Do you really think that's wise?
听着 就像我以前说的
Look, like I said before,
这个模式与我为投资人所做的完全兼容
this model is completely compatible with what I do for the Investors.
生意约好 我就越有跟他们谈判的筹码
The more it thrives, the better partner I can be for them and their business.
那要多久呢
For how long?
看你拓展趋势
Looking at the direction of your travel,
你是想要完全绕过他们吗
is your plan to escape from them completely?
你新的生意需要那个两亿美金 不是吗
You need that 200 million for your new business, don't you?
我听说有关投资者想收回这笔资金
I'm told the Investor concerned would like it passed over to him.
别让他等久了
Don't make him wait.
我为他们赚的钱远远超过了这个城里任何一个人
I've made more money for them than anyone in this city.
我们今天被袭击了 亚历克斯 现在不是讨价还价的好时机
We were attacked today, Alex. It s not a good time for negotiations.
我想我很清楚他们要什么
Pretty sure I know how they think.
无意冒犯 可能比你还清楚
Maybe even better than you. All due respect.
不好意思
Forgive me.
你觉得钱来的干净就是好人了吗
You think clean money means a clean soul?
发生在肖恩和你家人身上的事情 只是生意而已
What happened to Sean, to your family...it was just business.
滚
Fuck you.
你在自讨苦吃
You've bitten the hand that feeds you.
你一定会被反咬一囗
Don't be surprised if it bites you back.
你应该让我处理这些
You should have let me handle this.
祝你开会好运
Good luck with your meeting.
停止下一次交易 我这里出了点问题
Hold off on the next delivery. There is an issue on my end.
没什么大事
Everything is okay.
我晚点和你细讲
I'll share details later.
请确认不交易 我等你指示
Please confirm no delivery. I'll wait for a call.
宝贝
Honey.
给我留一片 好吗
Save me a slice, yeah?
-我在等人 麻烦叫他们直接在天台等我  -好的 杜马尼先生
Uh, I'm expecting guests so send them up to the terrace.
阿西夫
Asif.
爱德
Ed...
投资人讲的很清楚了
The Investors have made it clear.
任何人越界了都会被处理的
Anyone who acts out of line is to be dealt with.
零容忍
Zero tolerance.
抱歉但我实在无能为力
I'm sorry but my hands are tied,
卢安 怎么了
Luan. What's wrong?
我们在说谁
Who are we talking about?
放下枪我们好好说
Just put it down and we'll talk.
坐
Sit.
你在为他们工作
You're working for them?
这简直太搞笑了
That's almost funny.
混蛋
Fuck!
你为他们杀了肖恩 你太狡猾了
You killed Sean for them? You fucking snake.
-我没有选择  -可怜的艾略特
- I didn't have a choice. - Poor Elliot.
你知道吗 你还活着是因为他们让你活着
You know, you're only here because they wanted you here.
现在他们不需要了 太麻烦了
And now they don't. Too much of a liability.
那你在等什么
What the fuck are you waiting for?
我们的老板们 所有的罪证
Our bosses. Years of incrimination.
所有的犯罪记录 都在这里了
Years of wrongdoing. It's all there.
-肖恩给你的  -不能交给警察
- Sean gave you this? - Can't go to the police.
法庭 媒体 都是投资人的天下
Courts. Media. The Investors own it all.
但你 这个
But with you, this...
这是我们唯一的出路
this is how we get out.
你想勒索投资人
You want to blackmail the Investors?
只有你知道怎么做
And you'll know how. Better than anyone.
我一个人做不到 亚历克斯 我试过了
I can't do this by myself, Alex. I've tried.
但你知道可以找谁 达成交易
But you know who to contact. Make a deal.
好好想想
Think about it.
我父亲 你的家人 我们两个
My father. Your family. Both of us.
一起来保证这个安全 好吗
This will keep us safe, all right?
当时我能做什么
Was there anything I could have done...
来保护肖恩吗
to save Sean?
没有
No.
打开你的电脑 看看这些文件
Open your laptop. Look at these files.
快点 亚历克斯
Please, Alex.
他们会找到我 他们会杀了我的家人
They'll find me. They'll kill my family.
我不能让这些事情发生
I can't allow that to happen.
去找香农 她需要你
Go to Shannon. She needs you.
什么
What?
照顾好我父亲
Watch over my father.
别 亚历克斯 别
No, Alexl Stop!
你赢不了他们的
You can't beat them.
别 亚历克斯
No! No! No...Alex!
没有新的留言
You have no new messages.
祖思 怎么了 宝贝儿
Zeus. What's up, my boy?
要来点芝士吗
You want some cheese?
来 来
Come. Come.
来
Come.
要去尿尿吗
Wanna pee?
来吧 去
Come. Get out.
醒醒 姑娘们 快点
Wake up, girls. Quick...
爸爸
Papa?
怎么了
What's happened?
-发生什么了  -没事
- What's happening? - Nothing.
-发生什么了  -进去
- What's happening? - Go inside.
-有些不对  -带女儿们进去先
- Something's wrong. - Get the girls in first.
进去 宝贝 进去
Go, babe, go.
妈妈爱你们
Mummy loves you.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what's going on.
-轻点 带上你妹妹  -发生什么了
- Quiet, take your sister. - What's happening?
-没事  -别老是说没事
- Nothing. - Don't tell me it's nothing.
-听着  -发生什么事了
- Listen to me. - What's going on?
-保险箱的密码是什么  -什么密码
- What's the code to the safe? - The code?
你生日 告诉我发生什么事情了
It's your birthday. But tell me what's happen...
真的没事 和女儿们在一起
Everything's okay. Stay with the girls.
卢安
Luan...
Luan!
科巴
Koba!
太 迟了
Too... late...
梅玲达 梅玲达
Mirlinda...Mirlinda!
妈妈呢 妈妈呢
Where's Mum? Where's Mum?
我是卢安·杜莎 我现在不能接听电话
This is Luan Dushaj. I can't get to the phone right now.
请留言 我晚点会回复 谢谢
Please Ieave a message and I'll return your call Thank you.